today I'm gonna be talking about how I
think about meditation and I'm you know
I've been I was reflecting on this
recently we just finished a retreat with
shin zenyatta he was at the monastery
there's this very significant for me
because you know as I've been practicing
now for about 12 years and in the first
year or two of my kind of practicing
life I've got introduced to Shinzon's
science of enlightenment audio series
like you know 20 hours long just
Shenzhen geeking out about how amazing
it is that meditation and science are
coming together and just been really
captured my imagination and really
propelled me along this path the factors
that I've been on now twelve the
monastery fervor for three years with it
if going to Cyprus year and a half which
if you don't know is a very kind of
weird bootcamp like experience of
meditation and all along the way I've
been very successful life
and it was partly having to do with the
same inquiry that shins and I was like
what exactly are we doing when we sit
down and are just quiet and we turn it
in so to speak and do something follow
our breath pay attention to our
sensations how can we kind of make sense
of what it is that we're doing such that
we have confidence
and creativity and such that we can sort
of allow our experience and our insights
to grow in accordance with an
understanding a conceptual understanding
of what it is that we're doing when we
sit now most of the kind of approaches
you find will say something like if you
do this meditation then you will
experience these benefits but there's a
missing piece there right like why is it
that you will experience these benefits
right so if I drop an apple from my hand
it will fall to the ground but what is
missing there is the theory of gravity
right so there's some kind of
explanatory power that we can access
I believe that helps us make sense with
what it is that we're doing when we
spend 100 hours on the cushions
observing our experience so unlike other
Sunday's that I would invite people to
ask questions like well I'm giving this
talk just because I don't want to like
lose you and then keep going
yeah can I ask you to put the mic on so
feel free to ask so the basic idea that
kind of where this whole frame starts is
that the recognition that as human
beings we have this perhaps unique
capacity
to look at things in different ways and
my favorite example to use for this is
like treats right now you could look at
that tree as a biological organism and
you can understand the way that it takes
nutrients from the soil you know it uses
sunlight to create energy so on and so
forth you can understand it as a
biological organism you can also
understand it as a resource right that
you could extract that you could take
and turn it to wood that you could build
a house with or perhaps the the leaves
are some kind of nice right that's a
different way of looking at what that
tree is you could also look at it as
some wisdom traditions do as a spiritual
friend that's another way of looking at
what it treats all of those ways of
looking are available to us as humans
and they may or not be may or may not be
accessible to us but they aren't
available to us humans we all have the
same kind of hardware that's capable of
accessing those diversity of ways of
looking and many more right and so for
any given thing there are many different
ways of looking so this is the the core
kind of thesis the the premise on which
this whole framework is based so I say
you can look at things in different ways
I mean you can you can sense things in
different ways you can relate to things
in different ways you can conceive of
things in different ways and ultimately
you're able to participate with things
in different ways that isn't an option
that's available to us that's here
so
the critical or one of the critical
insights for me is that out of each of
these ways of seeing a new world is
created and discovered so for instance
the resource acquisition lens right if I
put that on and look at the world
through that way of seeing certain
things certain understandings become
available certain paths open up
throughout history in fact to a large
degree we can look around and see ah you
know the world that we have created
together is in large part a result of
that way of seeing operating within many
human minds at once so the way of seeing
that sees the world and starts to think
what's relevant here is what I can
extract what I can turn into profit what
I can take and make into you know
products and resources what I can
capitalize and I said or you know the
way of seeing that we call science that
seeks to understand how it is that these
things work how they interlock with each
other so we can tell stories that allow
us to explain the way things are such
that we can create technology that's a
way of seeing
so the
one of the other pieces to this is that
there's not there's not any way to
escape this situation unfortunately you
can't say oh there are ways of seeing
I'm just gonna stop seeing things a
certain way I invited to try see you do
that and see what happens
you'll find that you kind of just go
into another way of seeing it seems like
everywhere we look there is a way of
seen to be found there's not like some
place that's free from ways of seeing in
fact that itself is the rather
pernicious way of seeing you'll find it
in many different philosophical systems
the kind of view from nowhere right the
idea that we're going to somehow look at
things as if it's the one way to see
things or beyond ways of seeing back to
is a way of seeing that takes itself not
to be able to see very confusing and
that's part of how they you know weasels
into your mind and occupies your
attention deep sleep
mm right yeah so there's no procession
there might not be yes yes indeed yeah
and then that is exactly right that's
part of what we're attempting to do in
meditation actually is is create less
and less we might say complex ways of
seeing funk discover less and less
fabricated ways of being in the world
and to resolve the will from heaven to
choose yeah yes yeah
yeah so most most of the ways of seeing
that we operate with are installed in us
by culture family upbringing so on and
so forth you know there are lots of ways
of seeing what a human being is but you
might try on it way of looking at human
beings that sees them as collections of
ways of seeing seeing yourself as a
collection of ways of seeing habitual
ways that you see and participate with
reality right subject/object
what am I going to do with my life how
many ways of seeing are kind of implicit
in that state my life what am I going to
do you see but this is an interesting
way of framing lots of different
situations and kind of questions so the
reason why this is all a big deal for me
is that we end up constructing our
experience through the ways of seeing
that we use and so like I said if you
have a way of seeing that seize
resources or you know sees people as
being means to end you create you end up
creating a world in which that is the
world you create an experience in which
that is the experience because you using
that way of seeing to organize the world
right and get me have that freedom and
so this is an invitation to recognize at
rekted with that freedom so different
ways of seeing create discover two
worlds different others different sexes
us
so when I just when I when I look at the
world in a science wet I create and
discover a scientific world oh the world
is so scientific so logical sort word so
rashly amazing when I look at the world
as sacred and divine I create and
discover a sacred and divine well dude
we have that freedom we can do either
one we have this and so you know of
course there are many different criteria
he might use to select what ways of
seeing you want to leverage anymore as I
said science has its own criteria like
soundness and symmetry validity evidence
so on and so forth and that's kind like
trying to do a particular fan and that's
beautiful
good propria in the context of most
forms of a buddhist interpretive
practice who say select ways of seeing
that reduce our suffering we take on
ways of seeing that reduce our suffering
we might also try out ways of seeing
that we can play with like meta which
increase the sense of kindness of
compassion and loveliness that's another
bucket but in general the kind of jewel
at the heart of the Dharma is the
collection of ways of seeing that erode
a root dampen and ultimately end
something and that happens by invoking
them by practicing them by learning to
see from this prescription is but it
means the number of ways of seeing that
the road suffer that lead to himself and
they do that oh yes everything's sense
of hearts
so the usual example that I give is the
three characteristics
it may not familiar with the three
characteristics so you'll probably know
them what I say the three
characteristics sometimes called the
three marks of existence or impermanence
suffering and knows the three marks
three characteristics often these are
presented in a lot of different learning
communities as kind of like truths to be
recognized or a body of like oh you
should understand that everything is
impermanent that all is suffering and
then you don't have a self okay like so
that creates interesting philosophical
discussions perhaps but that's not how I
think oh I would argue we ought to
relate to these three characteristics
instead I would say I would interpret it
that the Buddha was suggesting three
ways of seeing that we can actually use
when we sit in meditation right so what
is it like to take on the way of seeing
that season what's most relevant in my
experience is that it is improved and
what does it mean to tune into that what
does it mean to really look at that what
does it mean to put that at the top of
my life relevance landscape in my
cognition in my mind in my perception of
my phenomenology what does it what
happens when I do that similarly what
happens when I really looked at what
creates suffering they notice as the
said that like anytime there's
resistance cleaning there's some amplify
suffer what happens if I just allow my
experience to be as this instead I just
take that that's the way of seen Wow Wow
or what if I notice that I can also take
on this way of seeing the tiny flight
this is it
everything is just sort of happened this
is kind of just happy there's not me
agent doing a thing really least I can
look at my experience that way where
things are just sort of arising and
passing away and I'm not doing anything
it's just what happens when we invoke
those ways of seeing is that clinging
yes weaker or lessened it's damp we let
go and when we let go there's my self if
there's an my favorite I'm John chopped
boxes you know if you let go a little
bit a little bit of peace if you let go
a little more over mark get setgo a lot
no no a lot of easy you let go
completely you'll know the peace of the
Buddhist so that's really what we're
attempting to do when they meditate is
in use take on ways of seeing that have
the result of causing us to let go is
why would we let go or why would we hold
on our things are perfect there's
passing away
watch this question if you want but
wondering about how the word suffering
even invokes the way of see compared to
some of the other translations of dukkha
or just fundamental dissatisfaction or
wondering if you might say that
yeah interesting
I'm not sure what you have in mind like
if I if I take the word suffering say
for instance if I'm doing
characteristics yeah
if I ask is this suffering it's like
sometimes it doesn't match my answer
last does this satisfy it's much more
resonant yeah so when I think suffering
or when I hear the word suffering
it doesn't seem can capture doesn't seem
like it seems like that's a way of
seeing itself a lot of people tend to
bring to it which kind of doesn't work
for me yeah yeah well so I think the key
among yours what you said is it doesn't
work for you right and so one of the
things that I most appreciate about this
having this frame is that it enables
that kind of sense to go what is like
I'm not doing this because like somebody
gave me this reitman ritual I'm just
gonna like follow my breath a million
times and tell something happens I'm
happy right I understand what it is that
I'm like kind of attempting to
accomplish here
and for me like oh this understanding of
suffering doesn't really work like it
doesn't kind of land in my experience
right it doesn't allow me to release
plain and really suffering be happier
and so maybe it's more yeah it's
fundamental this fast factor maybe it's
more like I'm really curious about where
this is all going I want to know what it
means to unfair Akane my experience I
want to know what emptiness is it's not
about suffering it's not like the joy of
exploring what consciousness is capable
maybe that's more than your thing right
but it allows us to kind of get out of
the constrictions of dogma and like this
opposed to and enter into a more
creative playful life
I would say like a sovereign position in
relationship to our practice
that's a good question this is suffering
something that lands fear wasn't more
motivates and so
to a little bit of practice with that
see what happens
do they have any questions
so I'll just lay out what I'm intending
to do here so I'm going to do guided
meditation first we're gonna do a little
bit of samadhi practice concentration
cultivate a little bit of well-being and
then we'll use that as a basis to
explore the three ways of seeing that I
mentioned the permanence suffering you
know self don't feel like you have to
follow along if you wanted to stick with
some audience just keep cultivating a
sense of well-being a calm and peace do
that if you get to be impermanence
characteristic and it's really jamming
for you and you like it it's good just
stick it back don't move on and yeah but
also feel free to try all three like if
you don't get this issue to go to
practice so there's a link there we
don't like so how does meditation and
your view work what would as manatee
should do in the memory of that what
does meditation do it
yeah okay thank you yeah so in this
frame we might see that meditation
accomplishes a couple of things one is
this a way to release ourselves from the
ways of seem that have been installed in
us by our culture by our family
and this is extremely essential in
today's world because the ways of seeing
that are currently operating on our
planet is hurtling us towards extinction
or the possible a decision so we need to
sort of uninstall the current operating
system and meditation you can do that by
leveraging ways of seeing that reveal
the emptiness of all the ways of seeing
including the ones that have been
installments agriculture the other thing
that it allows us to do is to play with
new existing right once we kind of get
into this ability to deconstruct our
perception and our ways of seeing that
have been installed to us we can then
playfully deploy new ones right so we
can see that maybe what was it like to
live in a world in which like everybody
is my friend made a traditional way of
seeing that the Buddhists recommend all
our my friends you know may all be happy
it's a way of seeing and you live from
that it creates a different world and
maybe that world maybe that way is
participating world is is more
appropriate more useful now or leads to
more activists or more well-being or joy
later and so it gives you that sort of
like platform for experimentation as
well
so let's right now
to begin invite you to straighten that
we find a posture that feels a lot
aligned
and as possible as a sense of nobility
might be possible to find the kind of
energetic tone of alertness of the life
as you can get into that fashion
and I need to open up to your experience
you're
quality of your
[Music]
they're somatic experience
checking it
so the idea of this first practice smadi
practice is to cultivate the sense of
energized calm and one way to do this is
with the breath
there are many ways to breathe that help
to cultivate this sense of peace
well-being ease pleasure it's all
suggest
whew
find one that works
in general just
welcome and pay attention to any feeling
of ease
with mammals
that you can try
is breathing along
extending the exhale
meaning to force
we also try
tuning into the restful
whether so or breath tends to carry with
it some sensations of restfulness
particularly the out-breath
to it
feeling with us
with this method can be helpful to to
notice anywhere you're holding the
tension in your body breathe
discovering restfulness
made also experiment
breathing and energy
cleaning out the elack's ation
yeah
the invitation here again is too
breathe or participate with your
experience in whatever way cultivating
successive
these
doesn't have to be profound heading in
that direction
this calmness ease invites the
unification
is vehicle
and just can feel
it's okay to just feel
I'm feeling good for no reason
is a radical just
I experiment
imagining that the breath
coming and going from the center
imagine yourself to be breathing from
your heart center
does it feel like
again any of these suggestions
whatever reason
it's interesting
as you continue your practice
and be interesting and useful to
experiment with seeing the breath in
various ways
what is good like to see the breath and
Cheney energy lifeforce
our design factual experience
news that waves
spirit
now what you're seeing because I'm
feeling
well what is it like to see the breath
[Music]
kind of love
what is not where you see
this way of seeing the breath is
available to you can be nice to breathe
in sense of receiving love
short break and then when they return
we'll explore the three characteristics
and in order for that exploration to be
very fruitful I recommend that you keep
the practice to your seat with
this state of calm whatever this tablet
- your posture
once again finding that tone and sense
very sensible
welcome
due to the characteristics
each of these will be treating as a way
of seeing
each of them dividing us to look at our
experience in a particular way
the way that according to the Buddha
practitioners leads us out of suffering
disease
towards regression
the first characteristic is
this
we're seeing
asks us to make relevant to pay
attention to the changing nature of our
perception
to change
caring less about what this chain and
more about that it is changed
you may notice it as kind of undulation
vibration
whatever it is tuning
can be helpful to use the label here
change change
as he tuned in to this
changing made of this quality needs
arises too
you don't need to try to let go
seeing impermanence causes
this way I've seen you can zoom in to a
particular part of your experience batch
increments
here
or you can
Express
is
if you find yourself getting tight
constricted
practice
the balance between
that's a very nice calm this
investigation is deconstruction did the
heart
this form of contemporary practice
you can practice
to explain characteristic suffering the
way of seeing
this
what I've seen you've access to notice
suffering on its we notice contraction
resistance
to
do a part of your experience
place your attention there
change that and so elegantly listen
suffering equals pain multiplied by
resistance
your experience
yeah you feel like it's not working
Oh
another facet this way I've seen
seeing connection between resisting my
perception that muscle body
notice that we're suffering
yeah adopting this way of seeing
decreases
creates
in any case this is why we practice ways
of seeing take time to develop to grow
well
we're seeing the world
philosophical idea here practiced as a
way of seeing
the experience is just happening
with this way of seeing
aspects of your experience may be more
accessible
suggest explore
various facets
nature
[Music]
experience
the last couple of minutes thank you to
explore whichever method he felt the
most interesting one seems most
accessible interesting
each of these ways of seeing is a path
each forms particular insects we might
be drawn to one too
so have some time for discussion so
how's that for folks if you want to
report I think you discovered was for
you make questions about anything this
is okay couple things I wish that I said
at the beginning of the talk one thing
is just this is what I love you know
partly this is a way that I've
discovered to think about this path such
that I can really fall in love with it
that's part of the for me the affordance
of this frame you said it affords me to
really fully love this path and then the
second part is that much of this almost
all that is inspired by a particular
teacher named Rocco bear who teaches
other guy housed in the UK so just so
you know happy directly to resources
but yeah so this is time questions to
know
like sense experience like hearing only
it was arising sound like we
distinguished it's quite revitalizing
inspired a little reflection about the
relationship between suffering and very
hard to see that distinction between
what is seeing and see yeah it's
fascinating how just like you have an
object you've seen itself just so
everybody knows John is a bit of like
really caught a plant in the audience in
the he is also deeply steeped and as
particular frame
[Laughter]
particularly suffering on the one level
in some sense letting it fully welcoming
it fully then it's another sense you're
like somewhat AC holding an intention of
like wanting it like not to be there
like that's why you're meditating some
sizes either better that's a bit like
you described it as like like the reason
we adopt these ways of seeing is because
they were do separate me yeah curious
your thoughts on that session yeah it's
tricky I think though that we can make
this kind of tension a lot easier body
really just getting into our
phenomenology right just getting into
our actual experience moment by moment
and in that we can notice like am i
actually resisting my experience like am
i wanting it to change in this moment
and what does that do to my experience
right so we can this kind of
philosophical position like ah that you
are meditating and therefore you don't
want things to be the way they are
because if you did
and like we can kind of get wrapped up
into that but it seems paradoxical and
yet we can find ourselves sitting and
see if that is actually present then in
that moment and if it is you will find
that if we can release that desire for
things to be other than they are but I
found I was in a very pleasant state by
the end of the first meditation period
and then in the second one because I've
been trying for what was coming next and
I had a sense of life and I was like
hoping to get back into that state but
when I got back on the chair it was like
yeah I would be 10 15 20 minutes to get
back here and so there's like this this
tension now I'm wondering if there's a
way of steam to release these real
subtle expectations some things going is
stirring away which seems to be a huge
obstacle for me which is also good
because it's workable
it's like knowledgeable that I learned
from having to continuously overcome but
I'm wondering if there's a way of seeing
you might offer to kind of like let go
of this level grabs me for like success
I do actually
this is what I've been playing with
recently I don't love it okay so this is
not as far as I know they prescribed
whatever seeing Buddha but nonetheless I
find it very active so the way this one
works you can you can do it right now
and you ask yourself what is here if
there is no problem
[Laughter]
do that again
ask that question again so you know one
of the functions of the mind is to
create and discover the problems and so
this kind of short circuits that
tendency to be very good with
expectations and things like that very
helpful
thank you I'm sorry for being late I'm
injection means I have the paradox of I
think I'm hearing it here and other
people's on the one hand we have the
luxury of many techniques and ways of
seeing and we have a profound
appreciation as meditators if you change
your mind you change the world as far as
you see it and that's so powerful in
itself around a little of slowing down
into various freedom to choose
perspective a new age churches and we
weren't sure what was going on but he
set up this semi golden and red tapestry
in front of everybody and then he was
welcomed by the community and started
business he said
we're going to see somebody which is now
hanging in front of us is part of a
worldwide meditation and it's a practice
distance sent out amongst of people that
if you teach people how to meditate in
the simple way that instead of
considering that your mind is somewhere
in your body the world
and you can choose perspectives with
your mind that all of this bodies and
things anything measurable is inside the
mind the mind is not something inside
the body and so he guided us into that
perspective
the world will be completely well they
said in the beginning that there came to
be a desire to not have endless choices
like how many hours do I need before I
have too many and I love that one who
can consolidate all these techniques
into an over
get going like get put feet on it and
give it but the need to resolve the
experimental mine without endless
perspectives in so body was too much we
mean I had heard too many kind of no
self things like there is no place my
favorite go on when I was growing there
is no place to seek the mind it is like
the footprints of the birds and so I
love that there is a consolidation and
an integration and a singularity point
and that's part of Samadhi or xarna visa
something's going on here that resolves
the endless decision maker what
technique is appropriate for this
in this place I've heard many here in
this community talk about how I was
fumbling through my techniques and I
need to get one becomes humorous and
that's great so the resolution of
intentionality so that it can be
creative bouncy playful and at the same
time experience Samadhi active oneness
with full diversity the free will of
beings who could be no sellers but there
instead of playing not just no suffering
there play there created that's what I
kind of wanted to you know somehow
anyway I found it so that community that
can actually articulate something beyond
the mind by the attempt to coordinate
itself
I appreciate an honest attempt but I'm
still looking for the community that
embody I've seen individuals actually in
many stark communities
but best in my confession there is no
order it is hopefully I find offensive
poem which I try to resolve its both
contemplation and sketch on
contemplations couch I once supposed
that all thoughts the stand opposed have
given their existence to each other as
doubt knows
certainty as its mother so I sat midway
between the two to take no sides I
resolved to do then as long slight
unfolds the colors of the day or life's
breath expanse to cull clay Finity found
in each creations verse and echoed for
my years as our God might differ through
nature's baths he seemed to speak
commits the truth if just one piece then
singing said to me when Finity
it is inconceivable be on your spiral
shadows and dress it in divinities plume
the one thing that does come to mind if
there's a lot that I don't know how to
respond to in what you showed but the
what does come up to me is is something
you said about the postmodern spiritual
marketplace and for me that's very much
at the heart of what I appreciate about
this friend is that it helps us see that
all of the various teachers and products
in the marketplace are invitations to
ways of seeing and inviting you to see
things differently
and to practice that kind of perceptual
training but really they're all
equalized right it helps us sort of cut
through the and sort of see
what they're actually offering without
being deluded by marketing essentially
which is today's yeah I appreciate it
yes I can see that you can't have
leadership whatever what would you look
at the different products in the
marketplace and choose them as select
them as ways of seeing isn't a way of
seeing meeting before you even in mark
and that way it sees itself a product in
the marketplace yeah and to a certain
degree it's like you you try something
out you see how it goes for you
and so the the thing that I it's also
important to say and kind of presence is
this is what that's attempting to invite
us to look at with the practice right
it's like when you do this practice ease
comes and you can trust that
directionality but you can just keep
moving in that direction the less that's
more simplicity of releasing complexity
and according to the Buddhist
contemplatively Max and this is the only
way to see what we're doing or the best
way but it is I think what is being said
here is that the directionality is
towards less is tours no thingness right
and so you can try different way they've
seen but the proof is inputted right are
they a doorway to less less suffering
less in fact perception less complexity
and so that becomes then the kind of way
of seeing that helps you make sense out
of the other ways of seeing right do
they actually work to afford that
reduction attraction or meditating
suffering if we're open towards less
close but it seems to be you know is
scientific phenomenology of
consciousness it's not an infinite
regress about coming from some sort of
mindset I can't get out of the
conditioned mind it's that the open bar
is already
yeah and anything he looks at tends to
give up its idealism oh I am the best
idea you know there is no best excessive
pure conscious won't be this well
devotion that is not conditional that's
not that this but we came twelve it out
or you can experience and fails to the
other it's not an idea right it's an
experiential proof now the patient by
the Buddha your your lamp unto yourself
and if you can't get confidence in the
practice some sky pockets when you get
it if you can't in yourself know what is
true by your own honesty how will
anybody
so I came here having many have you been
trained in a few spiritual practices
Native American spirituality science
mind and cousin immunity you know you
doing Native American spirituality at
the monastery in some in a variety of
ways and Shin said we're up in the
Church of religious science so and I put
a lot of effort into those as much
effort as you seen me put in here
because I wanted I needed to find a
spiritual path that worked for me
primarily to reduce suffering I consider
it
I meditate because it's healing and so I
come here and you're right everything is
just brought down it's more much more
elemental Native American spiritual is
perfectly infinite in the things that
you can do there and science of mind is
also very infinite and I found when I
came here in December of 2012 as I hey
it happened to me right away I had
gotten so far out into this huge
universal mind that I was completely
lost and came here and I sat here one
time and sorry you just packed me
Thanks I'm here
and so I that's what I appreciate about
the practice is and I was thinking of
Jeffrey said and I believe you said it
in your talk - I was thinking about is
it it's not really faith like I don't
have faith in the practice mm-hmm but I
trust the practice because I've
experienced that it works so even on a
night like tonight where I'm good I
never say myself I have a good practice
or a bad practice tonight I was not I
didn't I didn't do a very good job for
myself I'm very distracted by something
else and I think Jeffrey said it in his
poem because when I walk out that door
tonight and look up into the sky or
whatever's going on out there in nature
I'm gonna be fine because I trust that
and then we'll gradually be able to
break myself back to the practice I'll
probably think this a bunch more tonight
you know and so that's what I appreciate
in Canada practice in the weather we how
we describe suffering or this fairly
complicated concept of impermanence or
attachment more complicated there's
still very precise and very doable
then I have I have up trust in the
practice so I do appreciate sitting in
this room sorry don't have a deep
question but I just really enjoy the
order of things there's three there's
four doozy thank you for sharing that
what comes up for me was one of the
things I really liked about this
approach too is that it enables a level
of like creativity and autonomy if I
practice and so the first year that we
offered a Vision Quest at the monastery
I did the Vision Quest and that's big
leaders like sit in a cordon off piece
of the Woods would just sort of like
hang out for three days we do in this
container here good luck being there and
looking out into the woods and there was
a particular way of seeing that started
to emerge right but I was this way of
being with the natural world I had never
experienced before in my life
it was beautiful it was wondrous it was
really relaxing and what I can now do is
recall that way it seemed and sort of
turn it around on to my experience and
adopted them as the way I've seen right
that I can just like call up and just as
when you like participating look at the
sky right you can kind of do that same
thing we can understand that as a way of
singing turn use that to a doorway into
practice
and yeah